

# Anthony Greeley Software Engineer

### **Contact Information**



847 848 0552



tony.greeley@me.com



5054 N Winthrop Ave. #407 Chicago IL 60642

# Portfolio www.tonygreeley.com

# **Skills**

HTML/CSS/JavaScript Node.js MySQL Sequelize.js MongoDB Mongoose.js Express.js React.is **TypeScript** MacOS and iOS Apple Hardware Repair Pages, Numbers, Keynote Microsoft Windows Microsoft Office **GitHub** Test Driven Development Restful API Version Control

# **Objective**

Highly motivated individual seeking employment with a company that values their employees skills as well as embraces their individuality. Looking to become a javascript developer, in particular back end software development, as it is a key strength of mine and is where I hope my career takes me. Having worked in tech support for various companies over the past 13 years has given me a foundation for it. Problem solving with creative solutions has proven to be a valuable skill to help me excel in software development.

# **Employment Experience**

Apple Inc - Chicago IL

Genius, Family Room Specialist, Specialist

2010 - Present

- MacOS/iOS software troubleshooting
- Mac and Mobile hardware repair
- Employee training facilitation for new hired employees
- Employee development/training
- Creative thinking to diagnose issues
- Extensive knowledge of internal apple tools/systems
- Efficient in building rapport with customers and coworkers
- Provide custom solutions to fit individual customer needs

Verizon Wireless - Chicago IL

Retail Sales Representative, Data Champion

- 2006 2010
  - Facilitation of advanced device workshops
  - Development of coworkers in their roles
  - Assisted with sales goals and plan implementation
  - Custom solutions based on individual customer needs

#### Cingular Wireless - Schaumburg IL

Retail Sales Consultant, Acting Manager

2000 - 2006

- Helped customers with products and services
- Order, receive, and reconcile inventory
- Planned and prepared store meetings/weekly schedules
- Resolved conflicts for customers and employees
- Payroll and advanced administrative responsibilities

#### **Education**

Northwestern University School of Professional Studies, Cert Aug 2018 - Mar 2019

Colorado Technical University Online

Wheaton Warrenville South High School 1996 - 2000

#### References

Mark Thompson

Trilogy mthompson@trilogyed.com (773) 972-6275 **Sue Lippa** Trilogy slippa91@gmail.com (773) 551-1872 Miguel Caballero Bounteous

mcabs3@gmail.com (630) 803-1114